We all know about the health benefits of swimming.
我们都知道游泳对健康的益处。
It offers a great workout for the body – it builds endurance, muscle strength and cardiovascular fitness.
它是一项极佳的全身运动，能增强耐力、肌肉力量和心血管健康水平。
If you don’t mind getting wet, it can be fun too.
如果你不介意被打湿，游泳还能带来不少乐趣。
But who would enjoy swimming in water that’s ice cold?
但有谁会喜欢在冰冷刺骨的水里游泳呢？
Well, many people are taking the plunge, based on evidence that it can actually be good for us.
事实上，许多人都开始尝试这项运动，因为有证据表明，冷水游泳对我们的身体其实大有裨益。
Cold-water swimming – sometimes called wild swimming – involves swimming in natural areas including ponds, rivers and the sea.
冷水游泳——有时也被称为野外游泳——指的是在池塘、河流、大海等自然水域中游泳。
Jumping in gives a short sharp shock to the body, but many participants say they get used to it.
跳入冷水的瞬间，身体会受到强烈的刺激，但许多参与者表示，他们会适应了这种感觉。
A cold dip might wake you up, but research has found it can have much bigger benefits than that for your body and mind.
冷水浴或许能让人瞬间清醒，但研究发现，它对身心的益处远不止于此。
As well as being good exercise, spending time outdoors and by water improves wellbeing.
除了是一种很好的运动方式外，待在户外、亲近水域也能提升身心健康水平。
There is much evidence, mostly anecdotal, that suggests cold-water swimming has cured certain health conditions.
有大量证据——其中大部分是坊间传闻——表明冷水游泳能治愈某些健康问题。
One man who suffered constant pain after surgery claimed he was cured by taking a plunge in cold open water.
一名术后长期受疼痛困扰的男子称，在户外冷水中游泳后，他的疼痛就痊愈了。
And another swimmer, Sandria Simons, told the BBC “the immersion of your body in cold, salt water, just feeling like you’re at one with nature if you like, just feels amazing.”
另一位游泳爱好者桑德里亚·西蒙斯在接受BBC采访时表示：“将身体浸入冰冷的海水中，那种与自然融为一体的感觉，真的太棒了。”
But what is it that people are gaining from this chilly experience?
但人们究竟能从这种寒冷的体验中获得什么呢？
Doctors say getting into cold water evokes a stress response, but the more you do it, your reaction to stress is reduced.
医生表示，浸入冷水会引发身体的应激反应，但随着尝试次数增多，身体对压力的反应会逐渐减弱。
It’s also thought to have a strong anti-inflammatory effect.
冷水游泳还被认为具有显著的抗炎效果。
But there are bigger benefits to this stress-reducing exercise. Some experts believe cold-water swimming helps ‘cross-adaptation’, where one form of stress prepares the body for another.
而这项减压运动还有更重要的益处，一些专家认为，冷水游泳有助于实现“交叉适应”，即一种压力可以让身体为应对另一种压力做好准备。
For example, it also helps reduce the stress of exercising at high altitude.
例如，它也能帮助减轻在高海拔地区运动时产生的压力。
So, if you’re convinced that this is for you, take advice: approach it with caution, swim with a friend, and maybe start in the summer, when the water temperatures are higher!
所以，如果你确定自己想尝试冷水游泳，不妨遵循以下建议：务必谨慎尝试，最好结伴而行，或许可以从水温相对较高的夏季开始！